







Contact number: 8779830638, 09224277185 | Email id: pabaribhumi@gmail.com

Address: B/108, Veena Sitar, Mahavir Nagar, Kandivali-West, Mumbai- 400067.

PERSONAL SUMMARY

Bhumi is working in the field of psychology since past 5 years & has experience in conducting life skills training workshop for children, parenting seminars, workshops for teachers and wellness workshops for women.

Currently she is working at the Post of Senior Clinical Psychologist for a collaborative Project of Positive Parenting & Child helpline initiated by Parisar Asha & Cappemini.

She currently handles the unique initiative of Positive Parenting helpline and also conducts various workshops, psychometric testing and individual counselling therapy sessions.

Seeking to obtain a appropriate and permanent position of Sr./ Lead Psychologist with a public or private sector organization that values the professionals and offers room for career progression.

CAREER HISTORY

Parisar Asha

Senior Clinical Psychologist

June 2019-Present

Clinical Psychologist

June 2017-May 2019

Working for a collaborative project of Cappemini & Parisar Asha (Positive Parenting & Child Helpline).

Role & Responsibility-

- Developing workshop modules based on Effective Positive Parenting tips.
- Leading a team of psychologists and conducting trainings for them.
- Conducting workshops for Parents.
- Mental Health awareness workshops for teachers.
- Telephonic Counselling Sessions.
- Marital Counseling Session
- Individual Counselling Sessions.
- Psychometric Testing

Vidyartha Consultant (Counsellor)

January 2017- April 2017

Role & Responsibility Career Guidance

Anjuman-I-Islam, Begum Jamila Haji Abdul Haq College of Home Science(Affiliated to SNDT University)

CHB Lecturer(Visiting Faculty)

January 2017 - April 2017 (Subjects: Child & Youth Development: SYBHSc)

August 2014 – April 2016 (Subjects: Lifespan Development: FYBHSc & Child & Youth

Development: SYBHSc)

Indian Association for Promotion of Adoption & Childwelfare(IAPA) Counsellor

September 2014 – November 2016

Role & Responsibility:

- Developing workshop modules based on life skills and student relevant issues (e.g. Time Management, Anger Management etc).
- Interacting with families/teachers whenever need arises.
- Maintaining reports of workshops conducted.
- Contributing in and being on panel for selection of new counselors.
- Conducting training workshops for new counselors.
- Coordinating with organizations & schools.

King Edward Memorial Hospital (KEMH) Intern

September 2013 – October 2013 (2 months)

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION



Govardhan School of Yoga (Yoga Vidya Gurukul)

Diploma in Yoga Education, Ist Class with Distinction June 2016-July 2016

Indira Gandhi National Open University

M.A in Psychology (Clinical Psychology), Ist Class 2012 - 2014

College of Home Science Nirmala Niketan (Mumbai University)

B.Sc. in Human Development, Ist Class 2008 – 2012

REASEARCH AND VOLUNTEERING

Volunteer at "ISKCON YOUTH FOUNDATION" for conducting different social and cultural programs.

Member of Magazine Committee in college.

Conducted research project at KEM Hospital on the topic "A STUDY OF DEPRESSION IN MOTHERS OF CHILDREN DIAGNOSED WITH ATTENTION-DEFICIT HYPERACTIVITY DISORDER (ADHD) & ITS ASSOCIATIONS."

Date:

Place:

Bhumi Pabari